Douglas Pinheiro Goulart

Software Developer

linkedin.com/in/douglaspigoulart/ github.com/doougui douglaspigoulart@gmail.com

Summary

Being into software development for over 4 years, I managed to ship products which generated value and eased the life of more than 5000 users whilst improving the quality of existing software and creating new, valuable software from the beginning. Most of my experience comes down to working with JavaScript, TypeScript, React, React Native and Next.js.

Work Experience



Front-end Developer at Tecimob

Aug 2021 - Present (Remote)

By working as a Front-end Developer at Tecimob, I've been responsible for architecting as well as developing front-end solutions by using primarily React.js and its ecosystem. Besides that, I'm responsible for designing the UI, defining the overall technical architecture and developing our mobile application with over 5000 users by using React Native with tools like TypeScript, Styled Components, Jest, Git, etc.



Junior Full-stack Developer at QuikDev

May 2021 - Aug 2021 (Remote)

At QuikDev, I had the opportunity to maintain and evolve the enterprise management application Terravista. While helping more than 253 enterprises grow, I have made impactful results as a full-stack developer by making use of PHP with Zend Framework, Docker, JavaScript, jQuery and using SCRUM as an Agile Framework.

Education

Web development

CEDUP Diomício Freitas

February 2018 - December 2020.

Extras

Attended the "**Develop Android and iOS apps using a web programming language**" workshop at IFSC - Tubarão with a duration of 3 hours.